http://www.billypetersen.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This page was last updated March 18, 2019.
This privacy policy sets out how we [Billypetersen.com], uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.
Billypetersen.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Billypetersen.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
By visiting Billypetersen.com, you confirm your acceptance of this privacy policy.
Your continued use of Billypetersen.com following any changes to this privacy policy will be deemed your acceptance of any changes.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or would like to request access to your personal information or would like us to delete your information, please contact us at thewpap @ gmail.com
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA
Billypetersen.com collects personal data from site visitors when they leave comments on posts and/or email us via our Contact Form.
The data Billypetersen.com collects is laid out clearly in these forms, for example Name and Email Address.
Additionally, when emailing Billypetersen.com through the Contact Form, your IP Address will also be shared with us.
This information is not shared or distributed in any way and is only used to reply to your emails.
If you leave a comment on Billypetersen.com, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely.
Billypetersen.com shares content/articles from other websites.
By sharing content from other websites, these sites may collect information about you in a similar way and we suggest visiting any external sites own privacy policies to confirm how they will use your information.
COOKIES
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website to tailor it to our site visitor’s needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
SHARING AND RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA
Billypetersen.com DOES NOT sell, trade or rent the personal information of visitors to its website with others.
Billypetersen.com DOES use third party plugins where your demographic information (this does not include your name or email address) may be shared.
All comments left on Billypetersen.com are checked through an antispam detection service.
The plugins we use are created by Automattic.com which include Jetpack and Akismet.
Automattic also includes Gravatar, the global avatar service.
If you have signed up for this service, once your comment has been approved, your profile picture is displayed on Billypetersen.com.
You can view Automattic’s privacy policy here – https://automattic.com/privacy/
YOUR DATA RIGHTS
You can request to receive a file of the personal information held about you from Billypetersen.com.
If you choose to, we can delete this information, however this does not include any data we are required to keep for legal or security purposes.
Welcome Hey there, welcome to The William Petersen Appreciation Page.
Have news you think we have missed?
Get in touch
As a courtesy, if you repost original information from this website, please give billypetersen.com a shout out with a link back to this site.
THANK YOU, we really appreciate it.
Ages of the Moon Steppenwolf NOW
Streaming – June 2021
https://www.steppenwolf.org/tickets–events/steppenwolf-now/
Good Night, and Good Luck Steppenwolf Theatre
October 22 – December 20, 2020 (DELAYED)
https://www.steppenwolf.org/tickets–events/seasons/2020-21/good-night-and-good-luck/
Connect with Us
Instagram
XX - CSI - S4
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
#williampetersen
For those celebrating - Happy Thanksgiving
.
.
.
.
From Young Guns 2 - Pat Garrett
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
#w
That revealing end scene to Butterflied - CSI - S4
2008 press conference
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
#williamp
CSI - Bad to the Bone (S4)
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
#wil
Billy in DETACHMENT (2011)
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
#willi
CSI - Time of your Death (S6)
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
#
Billy & Bruno - CSI - Grissom’s Divine Comedy (S
Autograph RequestsSend a stamped self addressed envelope enclosing a photo you would like Billy to sign to the following address:
William Petersen
c/o Creative Artists Agency
2000 Avenue of the Stars
Los Angeles
CA 90067, USA.
To confirm, billypetersen.com does not supply autographs.
Site Archives Looking for something in particular? Browse our Archives or search the site using the form below.
Search for:
